<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- From: file:/C:/Users/fm/AndroidStudioProjects/gaaScoresStatsOrig5_6on/app/src/main/res/values/strings.xml -->
    <eat-comment/>
    <string-array name="minsPerHalf">
        <item>40</item>
        <item>35</item>
        <item>30</item>
        <item>28</item>
        <item>26</item>
        <item>25</item>
        <item>24</item>
        <item>22</item>
        <item>20</item>
        <item>19</item>
        <item>18</item>
        <item>17</item>
        <item>16</item>
        <item>15</item>
        <item>14</item>
        <item>12</item>
        <item>10</item>
        <item>9</item>
        <item>8</item>
        <item>7</item>
        <item>6</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>1</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="period">
        <item>1st Half</item>
        <item>2nd Half</item>
        <item>Extra Time 1st Period</item>
        <item>Extra Time 2nd Period</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="periodShort">
        <item>1st half</item>
        <item>2nd half</item>
        <item>ET 1st</item>
        <item>ET 2nd</item>
    </string-array>
    <drawable name="greenBG">#008800</drawable>
    <string name="app_name">gaa scores stats plus</string>
    <!-- From: file:/C:/Users/fm/AndroidStudioProjects/gaaScoresStatsOrig5_6on/app/src/main/res/values/help_strings.xml -->
    <eat-comment/>
    <string name="eventsListHelp">
<![CDATA[
<h1>EVENTS HELP</h1>    
<p>This screen lists individual match events recorded from the <b>MATCH</b>
screen.  IF you make errors in recording events they can be edited or deleted
from this screen. If you miss events, they can be inserted from here.</p>

<p>Tap on a match event to get options to edit or delete existing events or to insert
new events or substitutions</p>

<p>Inserted events are added immediately after the selected event with the same
time stamp<p>

<p><b>IMPORTANT SUBSTITUTION LIMITATION</b><br> 
 Substitutions edited or inserted from this page will be updated in the list of match
 events, in the list of substitutions on the <b>TEAM</b> screen and in the
 summary <b>REVIEW</b> screen.  However the team lineup used in the <b>TEAM</b> screens
 and in recording stats events is <b>NOT</b> updated automatically. If you want substitutions
 to be reflected in the team lineups you\'ll have to go to <b>TEAM</b> page
 and make the change manually
</p>

    
    ]]>
    </string>
    <!-- From: file:/C:/Users/fm/AndroidStudioProjects/gaaScoresStatsOrig5_6on/app/src/main/res/values/strings.xml -->
    <eat-comment/>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="no_names">No scorers recorded yet</string>
    <!-- From: file:/C:/Users/fm/AndroidStudioProjects/gaaScoresStatsOrig5_6on/app/src/main/res/values/help_strings.xml -->
    <eat-comment/>
    <string name="reviewHelp">
<![CDATA[
<h1>CONTACT DETAILS</h1>
<b>email:</b> gaaapps@gmail.com<br/>
Suggestions for improvements or error reports are welcome.<br/><br/>

<h1>HELP - REVIEW SCREEN</h1>
<p>
Summary of match stats is shown at top of screen.<br/><br/>

<b>*** Total Puckouts</b> - this stat is incremented every time you record 
a <b><i>goal</i></b> or <b><i>point</i></b> or <b><i>wide</i></b>
from the stats screen for the opposite team. <br/><br/>
<b>Total Shots</b> is the sum of <b><i>goals</i></b>, <b><i>points</i></b>, <b><i>wides</i></b>, 
<b><i>out for 45/65</i></b>, <b><i>off posts</i></b> and <b><i>saved/short</i></b><br>
<b>Scored</b> is the sum of <b><i>goals</i></b> and <b><i>points</i></b> 
<br/><br/>
List of match/stats events recorded is displayed at the bottom of the screen. Swipe up/down
to scroll.<br/><br/>
You can long press on any of the rows to delete that particular stats entry / match event.
Displayed scores and stats will be adjusted automatically where relevant.
</p>

<p>
<p><b>tweet match stats</b><br/>
What it says!</p>
<p>
Touch <b>share match summary</b> to email all recorded match data including: team selections, score, stats summary, 
cards, substitutions list of match/stats events recorded, list of scorers.
</p>



]]>
    </string>
    <string name="scorersHelp">
<![CDATA[
<h1>CONTACT DETAILS</h1>
<b>email:</b> gaaapps@gmail.com<br/>
Suggestions for improvements or error reports are welcome.<br/><br/>

follow twitter<b> @gaaapps</b> for updates and team downloads<br/><br/>

<h1>HELP - SCORERS SCREEN</h1>
<p>
Summary of scorers recorded using the 
<b><i>ENTER STATS</i></b> on the MATCH 
screen is shown for both teams.<br/><br/>
First Column is total scored per person. If no name was recorded for a score, the scores
are lumped together under unknown<br/><br/>
Second Column is scores from frees, penalties, 45/65s and sidelines.<br/><br/>
Third Column - <b><i>misses**</i></b> - is sum of wides, off posts and saved/short. 
</p>

<p>Swipe list to see all scorers if necessary</p>

<p><b>tweet scores</b><br/>
What it says!</p>

<p><b>share scores</b><br/>
Email the Scorers List</p>

]]>
    </string>
    <string name="scoresHelp">
<![CDATA[
<h1>CONTACT DETAILS</h1>
<b>email:</b> gaaapps@gmail.com<br/>
Suggestions for improvements or error reports are welcome.<br/><br/>

follow twitter<b> @gaaapps</b> for updates and team downloads<br/><br/>


<h1>HELP - MATCH SCREEN</h1>
<p>
<b>TIMER SECTION</b><br/>
Touch <b>start/stop</b> button to control timer.<br/>
Touch <b>mins/half</b> button to set timer length.
<br/>
Touch <b>1st half</b> button to set period of match. Extra time can be selected.
<br/>
Touch <b>-</b> or <b>+</b> button to increment or decrement timer by 30 secs.
</p>
<p>
<b>SCORES SECTION</b><br/>
Team names can be changed by swiping to the <b>TEAM 1</b> or <b>TEAM 2</b> pages.<br/>
Touch <b>goals or points</b> buttons to increase score.<br/>
Touch <b>-</b> buttons to decrease score.
<br/>
Touch <b>enter stats</b> button to get to stats recording screen.<br/>
Touch <b>undo last stats entry</b> to delete the most recent stats entry.
 (Note you can delete any previously entered stats entry from the <b>Review</b>
 screen.)<br/>
</p>
<p>
<b>ENTER STATS</b><br/>
You can record 1, 2 or 3 stats items per event - touch one item from the blue section,
touch a qualifying item from the orange section and touch an associated player from the green/grey section. <br/>
Touch <b>OK</b> to complete entry and return to SCORES screen.<br/>

</p>

<p><b>COMMENTS</b><br/>
Touch on the <b>comment</b> field to enter any additional details/info such as location, competition, hashtags for tweets, etc.
</p>

<p>
<b>MATCH EVENTS SECTION</b><br/>
The last four match events recorded in the ENTER STATS screen are displayed here. (Swipe to
the <b>STATS</b> screen to see the complete list of all match events.)<br/>

Touch <b>reset all</b> to delete all stats events, reset timer and reset scores to zero.
</p>
<p>
<b>TWEET/TEXT SECTION</b><br/>
To send Tweets, you need to have the Twitter App, or equivalent, installed on your device and you must
be logged in.<br/>
For texts, your device must be capable of sending sms messages.  You can setup the number or numbers to send texts to in the 
<b>MENU</b> section.<br/><br/>
Touch <b>tweet score</b> or <b>text score</b> to send the current score. 
The contents (if any) of the <b>comment</b> field
will also be included.
<br/><br/>
Touch <b>tweet score + last</b> or <b>text score + last</b> to send the current score plus the last stats/match event entered. 
The contents (if any) of the <b>comment</b> field
will also be included.
<br/><br/>
Touch <b>tweet selected</b> or <b>text selected</b> to get a screen with a list of: comment, score, the last 10 stats/match 
event entered. Touch on the items you want to include in the tweet / text.  Note that tweets are limited to 140 characters 
so you will be limited to 3 or 4 items.
</p>
<p>
<b>ACTION BAR MENU</b><br/>
<b>setup texts</b> - enter the phone number to send sms texts to. You can enter more than one number, just use a comma to 
separate the phone numbers.<br/>
<b>reset timer</b> - reset timer to 0<br/>
<b>reset score</b> - reset score to 0<br/>
<b>reset stats</b> - delete all stats events and reset stats summary to 0<br/>
<b>reset all</b> - reset timer, scores, stats and delete comment<br/>
</p>
]]>
    </string>
    <string name="teamHelp">
<![CDATA[
<h1>CONTACT DETAILS</h1>
<b>email:</b> gaaapps@gmail.com<br/>
Suggestions for improvements or error reports are welcome.<br/><br/>

follow twitter<b> @gaaapps</b> for updates and team downloads<br/><br/>

 <h1>HELP - TEAM SCREEN</h1>

<p>Touch <b>change team name</b> button to enter a new name for the current team. (Dont use 
duplicate team names. Always use a unique name.)<br/><br/></p>
<p>
<p>Touch <b>reset team selection</b> to reset all positions back to a number.  Note that player 
names already entered are saved for reuse.</p>
<b>TEAM SELECTION</b><br/>
Select the team lineup by touching any of the position buttons to get option to <b>enter 
new player name</b> or select from list of available players.<br/>
Repeat for each position.<br/>
To remove a player from a position, touch the button and choose option to <b>reset position
to number</b> or touch on an available player to swap them in.<br/><br/>
To change the name of an entered player or correct mistakes you need to delete them 
(menu option) and re enter the name.
</p>
<p>
<b>ADDITIONAL PLAYERS / SUBS</b><br/>
If you have more than 15 players it is best to enter all names before the start so that they 
can be swapped in as subs during the match. <br/>Add additional players by clicking on any position
button and choosing the <b>enter new player name</b> option. Repeat on the same button until 
all players on the panel are entered. Then touch on the position button again and swap back in
the original player selected.<br/><br/>
Touch <b>make substitution</b> or
 <b>make blood sub</b> to record a substitution in the list of match/stats events.
 You will be asked to select which player is going on and then select player coming off.
 (Note that the name of the player going on must exist on the team already i.e. their
 name must have been entered previously (see paragraph above).) <br/><br/></p>
<p>Touch <b>view subs/cards</b> to display list of cards and subs full screen<br/><br/></p>


</p> 

<p><b>tweet selection</b><br/>
To send Tweets, you need to have the Twitter App, or equivalent, installed on your device and you must
be logged in on Twitter.<br/><br/>
Touch <b>tweet selection</b> to tweet an image/picture containing your current team selection from 1 to 15. 
(Note that on some 
devices the picture may not be visible on the send Twitter screen but it will be added
when you send the tweet.)
<br/><br/>
Touch <b>tweet subs/cards</b> to tweet an image/picture containing your current team 
selection from 1 to 15 plus a list of cards issued and substitutions made 
</p>

<p><b>text selection</b><br/>
To send texts, your device must be capable of sending sms messages.  You can setup the 
phone number or numbers to send texts to in the 
<b>MENU</b> section of the <b>SCORES</b> page.
 Touch <b>Text selection</b> to text your current team selection/lineup from 1 to 15.</p>
<p><b>share selection</b><br/>
 Touch <b>share selection</b> to email your current team selection/lineup from 1 to 15.</p>
 
 <p><b>save selection to summary</b><br/>
 Touch <b>save selection to summary</b> to save/store the current team selection/lineup from 
 1 to 15 into the match summary data.  Use this option as often as you wish to record 
 how the team line up changes with positional changes and/or substitutions. Each selection
 will be recorded as an image and a text file, with a timestamp, and can then be 
 shared/emailed using the <b>share match summary</b> button on the <b>REVIEW</b> screen.</p>
 

<p>
<b>ACTION BAR MENU</b><br/>
<b>delete a player</b> - delete a player from the current team panel.<br/>
<b>rename a player</b> - rename a player from the current team panel. Select player to rename
and then type in new name. N.B. best not to rename a player while a match is running, the match
events, subs, cards data will not be updated with the new name. Rename before match starts.<br/>
<b>create new team</b> - create a new team, you will be prompted for the team name.  Note that
the current team, players and team lineup are automatically saved and can be retrieved later.<br/>
<b>load a saved team</b> - retrieve a previously saved team, you can select the name from a list. Note that a team
loaded in the other team screen will not be available<br/>
<b>delete a team</b> - delete an existing team, you will be asked to select name from list.  Note that 
currently active teams can not be deleted.<br/>
<b>reset current team selection</b> - reset all positions back to a number.  Note that player 
names already entered are saved for reuse.<br/>

<b>import team from text file</b> - see below.<br/>
<b>export team to text file</b> - saves the current team selection/panel to a text file
on the device storage. The text file is stored in a directory called GAA_App_Export.  The text 
file can be shared by email or uploaded to DropBox (or equivalent).  The text file is correctly
formated so that it can be imported by this App on other devices. (Youll probably need a 
File Explorer/Manager App installed which allows 
you to navigate your devices file system e.g. ES File Explorer.)<br/>
<b>auto import downloaded team</b> - see below.<br/>
</p>

<p>
<b>AUTO IMPORT DOWNLOADED TEAM</b><br/>
This option enables you to automatically download team panels which are made
available through the @gaaapps twitter account.  Go to the the @gaaapps
twitter account and click on the download link in the relevant tweet for the team you want (and 
you may have to do this twice depending on your device setup).
You must select the options to <b><i>download</b></i> the file, not just view it in a browser
or screen.  Once download is complete come back to this App and selecting
this option should automatically import the downloaded team.<br/><br/>

If it does not work check that a file named <b><i>appGAASCORESSTAT.txt</i></b> has been
downloaded to your <b>Downloads</b> folder.  If not, use the <b>import team from text file</b>
option below to manually find and import the downloaded file.

</p>

<p>
<b>IMPORT TEAM FROM TEXT FILE</b><br/>
This options allows you to type out a team/panel in a text editor or word processor, save or
copy or email etc. it to the device and then import it into this App.<br/><br/>
<b>Steps</b><br/><br/>
<b>1. prerequisite: </b> You must have a File Explorer/Manager App installed which allows 
you to navigate your devices file system e.g. ES File Explorer.<br/><br/>
<b>2. create text file: </b> Use a simple text editor or word processor to create
a file in the following exact format:<br/><br/>
<b>teamstart,<br/>
Anthony Nosh,<br/>
Jackie Tyrant,<br/>
Noel Stickey,<br/>
Joel Coen,<br/>
Tommy Whoosh,<br/>
Seanie MacNificent,<br/>
Sean Og OHelpme,<br/>
Michael Funnily,<br/>
Alan McLobster,<br/>
Eoin Lurkin,<br/>
Henry Shufflin,<br/>
Da Burke,<br/>
DJ Scarey,<br/>
Joe Cunning,<br/>
John Mullet,<br/>
Michael Nice,<br/>
Shane Hooley,<br/>
Michael Curtins,<br/>
Block Walsh,<br/>
teamend<br/><br/>
</b>
Firstline must be <b><i>teamstart,</i></b> (note comma at end of line)<br/>
Then enter one name per line with a comma at the end of the line<br/>
The first 15 names will be assigned to positions 1 to 15 in the 
order they are entered.<br/>
The final line must be <b><i>teamend</i></b> (no comma)<br/><br/>
<b>3. save file </b> save the file somewhere as a text file with suffix <i>.txt</i>  
(if using a word 
processor you will need to <i>save as</i> or "export</i> to a text file format).<br/><br/>
<b>4. get file onto device </b> transfer or save your text file onto your device
into a directory or location where you can find it. (email, bluetooth, sdcard, usb cable
etc. maybe used to get file onto device depending on what you are doing. <br/><br/>
<b>5. select the <i>import team from text file</i> option from the App menu</b> 
You should now be able to use your pre installed File Explorer App to navigate to the
text file and select it<br/><br/>
<b>6. change team name </b> The text file will be read in and a new team created.
Use the <b> change team name</b> button to give your team a meaningful name and you are done.
 <br/><br/>

</p>

 
 ]]>
    </string>
    <!-- From: file:/C:/Users/fm/AndroidStudioProjects/gaaScoresStatsOrig5_6on/app/src/main/res/values/styles.xml -->
    <eat-comment/>
    <style name="AppBaseTheme" parent="android:Theme.Light">
        <!--
            Theme customizations available in newer API levels can go in
            res/values-vXX/styles.xml, while customizations related to
            backward-compatibility can go here.
        -->
    </style>
    <style name="AppTheme" parent="AppBaseTheme">
        <!-- All customizations that are NOT specific to a particular API-level can go here. -->
    </style>
    <!-- From: file:/C:/Users/fm/AndroidStudioProjects/gaaScoresStatsOrig5_6on/app/src/main/res/values/strings.xml -->
    <eat-comment/>
    <style name="TextShadow">
        <item name="android:textStyle">bold</item>
        <item name="android:shadowColor">#333333</item>
        <item name="android:textColor">#ffffff</item>
        <item name="android:shadowDx">1</item>
        <item name="android:shadowDy">1</item>
        <item name="android:shadowRadius">1</item>
    </style>
    <style name="TextShadowB">
        <item name="android:shadowColor">#333333</item>
         <item name="android:shadowDx">1</item>
        <item name="android:shadowDy">1</item>
        <item name="android:shadowRadius">1</item>
    </style>
</resources>